

PROFILE

Spirited and outspoken game developer, with 2+ years of experience, specialising on mobile.

With a taste for art, organisation, and human development.

Enthusiast of many fields and disciplines, with a preference for plain communication suitable for non-specialist.

But ultimately, a man on a mission to create places of joy in life & work.

INFO

Country of Residence:

Venezuela

Willing to Relocate: Yes

Phone No. +58 (412) 099 48 94

Email:

jaykozatt@gmail.com

Portfolio:

<u>jaykozatt.github.io</u>

Blog:

jaykozatt.medium.com

JAY KOZATT

Gameplay Engineer

EXPERIENCE

Game Developer - Freelancer

MAY 2023 - PRESENT

- Recreated gameplay from scratch using video as reference.
- Created a system to endlessly generate random levels..
- Redesigned an app icon for use in the Play Store.
- Matched and completed a previously incomplete walking animation in pixel art.
- Worked on released titles:
 - o The Path

Unity Developer - Self-employed - Team Leader SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Organised a long-term project following agile methodologies.
- Established a relationship with renowned Noodlecake Studio for potential future release of our title "All Bets Are Off!" under their publishing umbrella.
- The main driving force behind most game design decisions.
- Designer and implementer of systemic gameplay solutions.
- Both director and artist, involved in the art creation of our projects.
- Released titles:
 - o All Bets Are Off!
 - The Prisoner: Dread or Trust
 - Gaia's Revenge (Prototype)

Unity Developer @ Studio Dread

MAY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Programmer at budding indie studio under revshare model.
- Spearheaded a significant part of the initial organisation efforts of a team of 12 developers, and the core project structure.
- Assessed and reviewed game design decisions.
- In charge of implementing core game mechanics & systems.
- Co-lead the art direction of our projects.

Student Assistant @ BWL Teachers' Lab

Universidad Simón Bolívar JAN 2020 - JAN 2021

- Reorganised the lab's student personnel into a proper working structure, assigning specific responsibilities & clear domains.
- Developed the team's skills through workshops on several topics.
- Provided tech support for the lab on occasion as needed.

EDUCATION

Computation Engineering @ Universidad Simón Bolívar Caracas, Venezuela 2012 - 2020

INFO

Country of Residence: Venezuela

Willing to Relocate: Yes

Phone No. +58 (412) 099 48 94

Email:

jaykozatt@gmail.com

Portfolio: jaykozatt.github.io

Blog: jaykozatt.medium.com

TECH PROFICIENCIES

Game Engines	Unity Engine RPG Maker VX Ace
Unity Development Tools	Ink - Narrative Scripting Lang. ProBuilder Cinemachine DOTween Shader Graph (URP) Bézier Path Creator
Image Manipulation Software	Aseprite Illustrator Photoshop Paint.NET
Audio Manipulation Software	FMOD Studio Audacity
Programming Languages	C#, C++ Ruby Python
Database Managers	PostgreSQL SQLite 3